bemob.com 2011-12-29

# BeMob

Last Updated: December 29, 2011

This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected and utilized by mKhoj Pte Ltd ("BeMob" or "we", "us", "our"), its subsidiaries and affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy applies to the BeMob website at www.BeMob.com (the "Site"). For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is the UK branch of mKhoj Pte Ltd of The Heals Building, 22 Torrington Place, London WC1E 7HJ.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your data and how we will treat it.

BeMob is committed to respecting and protecting privacy for its publishers, advertisers, developers, and their consumers. This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to you, your company’s, or your consumers' data. For each element of data we collect, this Privacy Policy (referred to below as the "Policy") describes:

  * What data we collect.
  * How we use such data.
  * How we protect the data.
  * How you can change it or delete the data.

The Policy covers all aspects of our business, including:

  * Publishers and developers who are partnering with us to deliver services based on mobile advertising.
  * Advertisers and developers who are advertising goods and services through our network.
  * Interested parties visiting our website to access information or content.

By partnering with us as a publisher, advertising through our network, or visiting the site and/or using BeMob's services, you agree to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Policy, you may not access the Site or otherwise use the BeMob’s services.

BeMob divides its data assets into four areas: 1) account information that you provide to us and is required for us to conduct business with you. 2) anonymous or aggregated information that we collect to improve our product on your behalf. 3) UDID, which is recognized by us as sensitive information and handled separately; and 4) personally identifiable information.

## What personally identifiable information do you collect?

Personally identifiable information (referred to as "PII") is the most important category of data and we are committed to protecting this information and following best practices in this area. We view PII during the ad serving process (e.g. MSISDN), but do not collect it. We do collect PII during the account sign up process, but only with explicit permission from you.

↑ 

## You reference MSISDN as "seen" during the ad serving process, but not collected. Please explain what you mean?

MSISDN is sometimes observed during the ad serving process. This information, which can be linked to a consumer’s actual phone number, is often included in the header information coming from the consumer’s phone during the ad serving process. This header information is the source of anonymous data about the device and crucial to ad performance. Essentially, MSISDN is a by-product of collecting anonymous data about the handset used for targeting and reporting purposes. When viewed, we instantaneously encrypt it with a one-way hash encryption. The process nullifies its PII properties and offers the most robust protection available. We do not use MSISDN in our business. We do not link any other data to MSISDN. We do not share MSISDN (even after the one-way hash encryption process) with any third party.

↑ 

## What account information do you collect?

We collect personal account information that you provide including, but not limited to, name, address, email, phone number, twitter or social network profiles IDs, company name, and geography. This information is provided by you with your explicit permission as a means to conducting business with BeMob.

↑ 

## How do you use this account information?

This information is used to communicate with you, conduct businesses with you including reporting and payment, to provide you access to your account or information, and to generally improve your experience with our product and services.

↑ 

## How is my account information protected?

The personal account information you provide is stored in a secure fashion, behind a firewall, in one of our servers in either the US, Ireland, Japan, or India. It is stored behind multiple levels of authorization and access to this information is limited to BeMob employees on a need to know basis only and for the purposes of managing your account. This information is not shared outside the company and is only used to conduct business with you. We reserve the right to transfer this information as necessary within the confines of our firewall and server network. We also reserve the right to expand our server network to additional countries as necessary.

↑ 

## How can I change or delete my account information?

You can edit or delete your personal information by logging into your account at www.BeMob.com and editing the data.

↑ 

## What anonymous or aggregated information do you collect?

We collect anonymous or aggregated information from our business partners, their consumers, third parties, and site visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, blind cookies that allow us to identify site visitors in an anonymous manner, technical information about the handset (e.g. make, model, OS) demographic data (e.g. age, gender), location information (e.g. country, zip code, postal code, ISP), content type (e.g. games, finance, entertainment, news & information), ad type (e.g. text, image, automotive, travel, gaming), URL information of the ad being served, and information from advertisers about the post-click activity of the ads we serve. Given the harmless nature of this information and its benefits to our clients, we reserve the right to enhance or add anonymous or aggregated information at any time without notice.

↑ 

## How do you use this anonymous or aggregated information?

We use anonymous or aggregated information from 3rd party business partners and site visitors to enhance our ad serving, offer publisher ad filters and controls, provide general reporting capabilities, and personalize the site experience at www.BeMob.com. More specifically, the data is used to either provide pre-buy targeting options for advertisers, filtering options for publishers to manage ads appearing on their sites, enhance real time post ad impression delivery targeting using our Advertiser ROI Tracking Technology called AdROItÔ, and enhance services and reporting broadly. This information is not linked to your account information or PII. We reserve the right to share this information with third parties to improve our product or services.

↑ 

## How is this anonymous or aggregated information protected?

Anonymous or aggregated information is stored in a secure fashion, behind a firewall, in one of our servers in either the US, Ireland, Japan, or India. Access to this information is limited to BeMob employees on a need to know basis only and for the purposes of enhancing our products and services. This information is not shared outside the company and is only used to conduct business with you. We reserve the right to transfer this information as necessary within the confines of our firewall and server network. We also reserve the right to expand our server network to additional countries as necessary.

↑ 

## How can I change or delete anonymous or aggregated information?

This information is not and will not be linked to the personal information you provided or the personally identifiable information we collect. Therefore it is not possible, nor is it necessary, to edit or delete the data.

↑ 

## Do you collect UDID?

No, we do not collect the UDID of users. UDID is sometimes observed during the ad serving process. This information, which can be linked to a consumer’s actual mobile device, is often included in the header information coming from the consumer’s phone during the ad serving process. This header information is the source of anonymous data about the device crucial to ad performance. Essentially, UDID is a by-product of collecting anonymous data about the handset used for targeting and reporting purposes. When seen, we instantaneously encrypted using a one-way hash encryption. The process completely nullifies its PII properties and offers the most robust consumer protection approach possible. We never use UDID in our business. We never link any other data to UDID. We never share UDID (even after the encryption process) with any 3rd party.

↑ 

## How is this UDID information protected?

When seen, we instantaneously encrypt it using a one-way hash encryption. Once encrypted, there is no way to decrypt it and get the original UDID. The process completely nullifies its PII properties and offers the most robust consumer protection approach possible. We never use UDID in our business. We never link any other data to UDID. We never share UDID (even after the encryption process) with any 3rd party.

↑
